faboverfifty.com 2014-09-22

# Privacy Policy | Fab Over Fifty

## **PRIVACY**

This privacy policy (“ **Privacy** **Policy** ”) sets out how Brinsights LLC uses and protects any information that you give Brinsights LLC when you use the Site.  This Privacy Policy is part of the [Terms of Service](http://www.faboverfifty.com/content/terms-and-conditions) governing your use of the Site.  Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Service.

Brinsights LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.  When Brinsights  LLC updates this page, it will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.  If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of any such changes by posting a message on the Site. Brinsights LLC encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Brinsights LLC uses and protects your information. 

## **WHAT WE COLLECT**

We may collect the following information: 

. Name, age and job title

. Contact information, including email address

. Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

. Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

## **WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

. To improve the Site, including content, public user profiles, usability, offers

. To notify you about products, services and exclusive offers which we think will interest you. To contact you for surveys about subjects of great interest to you  

We may also use the information to customize the Site according to your interests.

We may also share your personal information with certain third parties without notice to you, as set forth below:

  * **_Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties_**.  We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions.  Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, hosting services, and processing payments.  When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.  We require such third parties to maintain the confidentiality of such information and to use such information only as necessary to provide us with designated services.
  *  ** _Legal Requirements.   _** We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a legal obligation, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Brinsights LLC, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (d) protect against legal liability.
  *  ** _Business Transfers_**.  As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets.  In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, your personal information may be part of the transferred assets. 
  * **_Advertisers.   _** We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other users, and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.  In these situations, we will not disclose to these third parties any information that could be used to indentify you personally.

## **SECURITY  **

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.  However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure of error-free.  In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.  Please keep this in mind when disclosing any information to us or any other party via the Internet.

We may allow you to communicate with other users of the Site and post information using message boards and other similar features available through the Site.  NONE of the information that you provide using these features is protected by this Privacy Policy.  THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO ANY INFORMATION (INCLUDING PERSONAL INFORMATION) THAT YOU PROVIDE USING MESSAGE BOARDS OR OTHER SIMILAR FEATURES AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE.  ALL SUCH INFORMATION IS PUBLIC INFORMATION AND MAY BE SEEN, COLLECTED OR USED BY ANYONE, INCLUDING THIRD PARTIES NOT AFFILIATED WITH BRINSIGHTS LLC.

**HOW WE USE COOKIES**

A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your customer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site.  Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.  The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve the Site in order to tailor it to the needs of its users.  We only use this information for the purposes of statistical analysis. The data is then removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us to provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you love and which you don’t. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Site.

On the Site, we may allow third party ad serving companies or ad networks to display third party advertisements.  Some of these companies may place a persistent cookie in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement.  Thus, these companies may compile information about where you are using your computer, where you saw their advertisements, and which ads you clicked on.  This information allows these companies to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.  We do not have access to the cookies that may be placed by these companies. 

## **LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

The Site may contain links to Third Party Sites.  However, once you have used these links to leave the Site, you should note that we do not have any control over any Third Party Site.  Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide to any Third Party Site. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and not to any Third Party Site. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the Third Party Site in question before providing any information to such Third Party Site. 

## **CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * When you are asked to fill in a registration form on the Site, you are provided with a User Account containing many options for controlling your information. Some information (specifically the Username you choose, your age and your home town) is made public on the user profiles for social network services: the user should consider this carefully before creating a User Account. The user is solely responsible for maintaining her User Account, choosing settings and account preferences to ensure they are up to date and to the user's satisfaction. 
  * If you have previously agreed to let us use your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@faboverfifty.com](mailto:info@faboverfifty.com). 
  * If you had a User Account created for you by a Brinsights LLC staff member, you are responsible for checking and verifying the account information entered on your behalf for accuracy, which includes checking or unchecking box that states you do not want the information to be used by anyone for direct marketing purposes.  We do not guarantee the completeness or accuracy of any account information or content submitted or services used on your behalf. 

## **CHILDREN**

## We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Site.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not give us any personal information.  We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information on the Site or any other website without their permission.  If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us through the Site, please contact us and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.    

## **ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION**

## If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to update or correct such information.  

## **HOW TO CONTACT US**

## Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices.  You may contact us at [webmaster@faboverfifty.com](mailto:webmaster@faboverfifty.com).
